onlinefaxes.com 2015-06-22

# OnlineFaxes.com | Privacy Policy

OnlineFaxes.com does not share, disclose or sell any personally-identifiable information (such as your name, address, telephone number or email address) collected online on OnlineFaxes.com sites with other unaffiliated companies or organizations for non-OnlineFaxes.com marketing purposes. In the future, should OnlineFaxes.com decide to share such data with third parties for marketing, it will provide notification and the opportunity for its users to indicate whether they would prefer that the Company not provide such information about them to third parties. Because this information is a critical part of our business, it would be treated like our other assets in the context of a merger, sale or other corporate reorganization or legal proceeding. OnlineFaxes.com also does not market to, or knowingly collect personal information from, children under the age of 13 on Company sites. 

**Acceptance of Privacy Policy**

By using OnlineFaxes.com web site and services, you signify your acceptance of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree or are not comfortable with any policy described in this Privacy Policy, your only remedy is to discontinue use of the OnlineFaxes.com service. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. Your continued use of any portion of OnlineFaxes.com web site following notification or posting of such changes, will constitute your accept of those changes. If you have questions or concerns about our specific policies, please contact us through our feedback form. 

**Opt-Out Options**

If you'd like to opt out of our system you can call us at (888) 201-4170 or [send us an email]().
